

Jenna Harris

Performance Engineer - Software Developer

PROJECTS (Demo Link ↑)

DAVIM Web Flow Visualization: 3D Web Race N Rumble: 2D Platform Arcade Game Night Terrors: 3D Platform Stealth Game Allyson Darke: 2D UI Card Game Prototype

EDUCATION

August 2020

B.S. Computer Science University of Houston

August 2017

A.S. Mathematics
Blinn College

WORK EXPERIENCE

November 2020- November 2023

Performance Engineer
(Manufacturing)

General Motors

August 2019 - December 2019

Web Developer (Internship) NASA

August 2019 - December 2019

Undergraduate TA (2D Game Creation)
University of Houston

January 2019 - August 2019

Undergraduate Apprenticeship (3D Web Virtualization)

University of Houston

SUMMARY

My name is Jenna Harris and I am a young professional affected by the GM Arizona IT shutdown. I bring professionalism, initiative and drive to all that I do and pride myself on my ability to adapt and overcome.

I hold 3 years of Performance Engineering experience involving client/server, web-based, and mobile-based applications. I am proficient with tools such as HP LoadRunner, APM Dynatrace, Grafana, Spark Jobs, and Sitespeed.IO along with manual testing via web Dev Tools and Fiddler. Project work flowed along Agile development pacing and release checks as needed. Applicable projects were set up to be automated via Jenkins and LoadRunner Enterprise.

Outside of my recent career, I have ~2 years of work as a full stack web developer via my NASA internship and university research apprenticeship project. For the internship, I worked with vanilla HTML5/CSS/Javascript and plugins such as jQuery, Bootstrap, to develop the front end for two websites. The work done for the apprenticeship was full stack web development focused on displaying data as a 3D render utilizing three.js. I also served as an undergraduate teacher's assistant for my college's "Intro to 2D Game Creation" where I supervised students utilizing photoshop and Unity to construct their own 2D game as well as help with any debugging they needed. Abstracts and further project details can be found on my project demo page linked in the top-right corner.

Contact

Email - jmhorn2015@gmail.com

Phone - 281-755-2281

LinkedIn - jenna-harris-3a8665175

Address - Gilbert, AZ 85295

SKILLS

HP LoadRunner, Load Runner Enterprise, APM Dynatrace, Grafana, Apache Spark Jobs, Sitespeed.IO, SQL Server, Oracle, Kibana, TruClient, Mobile App Performance Testing, Game Development, Game Design, C++ 11, Java, C#, Python, JavaScript, Github, D3.js, Three.js, A-Frame, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Amazon Web Services (AWS), Bootstrap, jQuery, Project Management, Selenium WebDriver, Augmented Reality (AR), Batch Programming, MySQL, SSH, Node.js, Agile Methodology, REST Methodology, CI/CD Pipeline, Scrum Methodology, XML, JSON